Bon appétit!
what is this?
in the middle of the water
I'm here at the main store!
Here we are!
Yay!
Ta-da!
Oh my God!
It's so good!
Hello everyone!
I'm Mina Matsuno, Sakusazuka46.
I'm Shizuki Yamashita.
What a surprise today!
The second ramen project!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
Last time, we went to Senri-Gan's.
We went to a ramen restaurant for our first Jiro-style ramen.
We just finished the first day of our tour in Fukuoka yesterday.
We just finished the first day of the tour in Fukuoka.
We're not back home yet.
But before we go home...
Fukuoka is our favorite city.
Tonkotsu (pork bone) ramen.
So today we're going to enjoy a little bit of it.
Today... what do you think?
Can you see it?
The first restaurant we went to was called Fukuchan Ramen.
It seems to be a very popular restaurant.
There's already a line of people waiting in line.
We'd like to get in line and try it, too.
Let's go!
We ordered ramen right away!
We've entered the restaurant!
I'd like to order right away...
Of course, it's our first time to eat here!
I thought I'd like to try ramen too.
I'd like to order ramen.
I'd like to have ramen!
Bon appétit!
Ramen order!
How hard do you like your ramen?
Hard.
Please order ramen.
Yes, please.
Like this
Our ramen
It smells amazing!
The steam is so hot!
It's warming up!
Oh, it's you!
Here it comes!
Yay!
I'm soaking it all up!
This looks so good!
All of it!
Wow!
Here it is, ready to be heated up!
Oh, wow!
Thank you very much.
Here it comes!
Yay!
It's all here!
Miso stir-fry for a snack.
I gave him two portions.
Milano Himuchi
Try it. Later.
Take a look.
Thank you.
Well, I'll get right on it.
I'm going to eat it.
Bon appétit.
Delicious.
Thank you for watching.
Oshii!
It's much lighter.
You can see it.
It's too good!
It's more spicy than the pork bone broth I usually eat.
I like the medium spicy one.
It's true.
The taste is...
It has a fresh taste and it's very thick.
It's very tasty.
It's very light.
Very tasty.
Thank you very much.
But it's very strong.
Yes, it is.
It's so good.
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
I'll have some too.
It's good.
Meat.
It's so good!
That's true.
My favorite type of pork!
What do you call it?
I know... Zakugi.
I don't know.
I like thin chashu pork too.
Yes, yes.
It's good.
What do you think?
I don't know.
I never thought I'd be able to come to Fukuoka for ramen.
I'm really happy.
Delicious!
The soup is so good!
Especially
It soaks into my tired body from yesterday.
Really.
I've been looking forward to it for a long time, today
Yes, Mr. Yuma, two one-eyed
Hai!
You always come with me and my ramen noodles, and you never let go
We take a bite and say to each other
We said to each other, "Oh, man...
Then we both go up the stairs.
And when we're done eating, we leave.
Afterwards...
I've been parting my bangs lately.
Thank you.
You look cute.
I'm very particular about it.
I'm sure you are.
Black?
Yes.
I mean, I've got it right above the dark eye.
Oh, yeah.
I think I got a perfect score today.
I'm measuring with a ruler.
This is what happens when you don't talk.
I'm going to run out.
Oh, my God.
What's this?
It won't open.
Oh, no.
I just finished it. It was delicious.
It was so good.
Thank you for dinner.
Thank you for the food.
The 300th customer in the store.
The 300th customer in the store, please.
Thank you for the food!
Thank you for the food.
Thank you very much.
That was delicious.
It was so delicious!
You probably can't imagine it from the looks of it.
I mean, it's pretty easy to eat.
It was really, really light.
Right now, it's really...
And the fight.
I kept turning it and eating it.
I finished it in an instant.
I wasn't hungry at all.
Hey...
Thank you for the food.
Here we are at the main restaurant.
Wow! Look at this.
Speaking of us, we've been to a lot of places.
We really love the list.
I think we've been there about 120 times.
It's a ramen restaurant where we often come together.
I've never been to the main restaurant.
It's always been a dream of mine.
I didn't think we'd be able to come the day after this tour.
I'm a little bit excited right now.
I'm from Fukuoka, too.
I'm from Fukuoka, too, but I've never been to the main store.
I'm so happy.
This is it. This is it.
The usual, the usual
And the music.
It's very relaxing.
I can sing.
I can sing. Oh, my God, I can play.
Maybe I can play the piano.
I can play the piano.
Okay, let's pause.
I'll have a drink.
Okay, I'll order an orange juice.
I'll have a Coke, my favorite drink.
Okay, then.
One, two, three.
Oh!
Oh, here it comes!
This is the moment.
Really.
I love it.
This is it.
This...
It's different.
It feels bigger.
This is more like the main store.
This...
The announcement tape.
You're right.
I don't think I can get a shot from here.
Orange juice.
That's us.
It's on the blog.
I've written about it before.
It's the exact opposite.
You know...
Tenements...
Triple or quadruple.
Recently promoted to 3x
Yes, sir. Excuse me, sir.
I'll leave you to it
Excuse me, sir.
Excuse me a moment, please.
Here.
The list.
It's a list of things.
I often read it while I eat.
It's good, isn't it?
How to eat it.
Maybe everyone...
Please read it.
I really do.
Excuse me.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you very much.
This way, please.
Please wait a moment for the rest of the items.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
The cola bottle is ready.
Is this the best flavor?
I like the bottle.
Cheers.
Bon appétit.
Mmm, that's good.
It stinks.
You did it.
You want me to go this way?
I'm excited.
When was the first time you ate a list?
I don't know. I was in school for the first time.
I like ramen.
I have a recommendation.
He used to take me to ramen restaurants.
I went to many places, not only the list.
Oh, I see.
I went to my hometown for the first time in junior high school with my friends.
I thought it was delicious.
I've been going there ever since.
Oh, here it is!
Here's the cream.
Is this quadruple?
This is quadruple.
It's glowing.
You know, I think I see that a lot.
Here it comes.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
Sir, if you'll excuse me, please step forward.
Yes, Lau is here.
Here you go, sir.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
You, too, Lau.
Ta-da!
I see this a lot.
Seino-san!
Bon appétit!
Oh, my God, I'm so excited!
I'm going to eat!
I don't know what I'll do.
Ta-da!
It's what I've been waiting for.
I mean, it's been a long time coming.
But I haven't eaten recently.
So I'm really happy.
The list of my long-cherished wish is really...
It's amazing!
Look, look, it's delicious!
You know that one day after work...
You know that day when we both really wanted to eat there after work?
Yeah, yeah...
It was so good!
Look at this.
It looks so good!
I didn't put the sauce on the fillet first.
I'll take a bite from here.
Bon appétit!
It's so good!
I knew it!
It tastes so good!
What is it?
It puts me at ease.
It's really calming.
Oh, my God.
It's delicious.
It's so good!
So good!
It's different from Fukuchan Ramen!
Thin noodles again, but with one layer!
The ramen I just had...
The soup has a strong flavor, but it's just right for the noodles.
The soup is light.
I feel like I'm eating the noodles.
Katamari Ramen
Fukuoka ramen noodles come in different types.
I tend to order Nagayama, which is the exact opposite.
What kind of noodles do you like the most?
I like Nagayama, but I've never met anyone who likes Nagayama.
I like noodles too.
Really?
Yeah.
I'd love to meet him.
Let me know if you'd like to leave a comment or something.
I don't know.
I'd love to meet him.
He says he wants to have a marble.
Hey!
My Kaidama is always like this.
Okay, okay, let's see.
I'll serve you some tea.
Thank you very much.
This is it!
Chalgraun. I played the current Kaede music in front of the class.
The report? Please listen to it.
Listen to this. Act like you're cherry blossoms are blooming.
Listen, please, Chalgraun.
Maple music.
Great. Yes, that's right.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you very much.
Please.
Hmm.
What is it?
I was on tour, on the 10th, and I just had a chance to pass by the list.
All the seniors saw the list, and they all said the list, and they all wanted to eat there, and the seniors were like...
Hey, you know, I'd like to take you there sometime.
Once, you know, I want to rent it out. At Cherry Blossom.
You can see the whole floor next door, like members.
We don't have any more.
But, you know, where we eat.
Okay, Mio's next.
Next.
Second one.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Delicious.
I like the one on the list with the half-boiled salted egg.
I know what you mean.
I usually order it when I'm really hungry.
When Shizuki-san said it, I asked for a boiled egg.
I was so bad at it.
Shizuki had finished all his ramen, but he was still looking at it.
Still facing that way? How long are you going to keep going? It was like...
Yeah, he's always next to me, and he usually doesn't talk when his ramen comes.
While I was eating, he said something like, "I'm going to boil an egg.
I was eating it with my breath on it, and he said something about not being able to face it.
But I don't really help him. I'm too busy eating my ramen, so I don't help him.
I peeked over to see if she was already eating, and she was still facing me.
I was like, "Hey, why are you still going?
While I was waiting for the next staircase, I looked over and he was still facing the staircase.
I was like, "Too late!
I was like, "How long am I going to be facing that way?
It was fun, wasn't it?
Excuse me.
If you'll excuse me, please wait a moment.
Yesterday was a fun first day, wasn't it?
That's great!
We've finished eating.
We'll continue now.
Kaede will be here soon.
Go this way, then.
You want to fish with me?
Yesterday, the first day of the tour.
We finished up two days after school.
It was fun.
You only say "yes.
I've been on tour.
I'm so thankful that the waiting time is getting smaller and smaller
I'm really thankful for that.
I've come to think
Like, "I've got to get changed in a hurry.
"I have to go to the next place...
"I have to hurry to change my clothes" or "I have to go to the next place"...
That's all.
Here you go.
Here it comes!
Excuse me.
Is this Chouyama?
Choyama.
It's different, isn't it?
It's different.
The noodles are a different color.
The firmness is visibly different.
Bon appétit!
Excuse me.
Maybe they put it in.
Thank you for waiting.
It's okay.
It's done.
Well, thank you very much for dinner.
Thank you very much. It was delicious.
I really want to tell you...
I've been wanting to tell you how I feel.
I'm sorry. It's nothing.
The second restaurant was Ichiran Honten.
I was so happy to be able to come to this restaurant that I had always wanted to go to and had always dreamed of visiting.
I also want to keep going back to Ichiran from now on!
It was the first time for me to come to Fukuoka for the first time.
I was also very happy to eat authentic Fukuoka Hakata Ramen.
I was also very happy to be able to visit the main store of Ichiran Ramen, which has always been a great source of support for me.
Thank you very much!
This is the second time I've eaten here, and I can't wait to eat more!
I hope you all want to see it, too.
Please let me know what you think of the flavors when you try it!
I'd love to talk with you!
Please subscribe to the channel and click the good button!
Bye bye!
Enjoy the next video!